techliquadators.com 2008-06-14

# BestBuy.com Help: <Topic>

This notice provides highlights of the Best Buy Privacy Policy. The highlights and full privacy policy apply to Best Buy retail stores, our Web site at www.bestbuy.com and other locations where we may collect personal information.

Personal Information  

  * We may collect personal information such as your contact, billing and shipping information. We may also collect demographic information.
  * We collect information regarding your interactions with our Web sites using cookies or clickstream technology.
  * We may obtain additional personal and non-personal information from third party providers.

Uses of Information  

  * **Best Buy does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties**. 
  * We use information about you to fulfill your requests, administer various programs, provide services, and for other business purposes.
  * Your personal information may be shared with current or future Best Buy entities or subsidiaries.
  * We may also use the information you provide to send you marketing communications. 
  * In limited circumstances, Best Buy may need to share your information with certain third parties to perform services on our behalf.

| 

Your Choices  

Important Information  

  * Best Buy does not knowingly collect information online from   
children under 13. 
  * The Best Buy Companies value our relationship with our customers and we are committed to responsible information-handling practices. View our entire Privacy Policy. 

How To Contact Us  

If you have questions about Best Buy's Privacy Policy, contact us by:

**Phone:**  
1-888-BEST BUY (1-888-237-8289)

**E-mail:**   

**Regular mail:**  
Best Buy Corporate Campus  
Attn: Privacy Manager  
7601 Penn Avenue South  
Richfield, MN 55423-3645  
  
---|---  
  
OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT TO OUR CUSTOMERS   
Best Buy Co., Inc.

We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices. 

The Best Buy Companies follow these privacy principles both online and offline in the collection, use, security and sharing of customer information: 

  * **NOTICE**. When we ask for your personal information, we will tell you why we need it and what we will do with it.
  *  **CHOICE**. When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts.
  *  **SECURITY**. We will use reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we receive from you.
  *  **SHARING**. When we share your information with other companies to help us provide our services to you, we will require them to comply with all applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information. 

Best Buy Co., Inc. is the parent company of the Best Buy Companies, and as such, if you provide information to any of the businesses, stores or Web sites owned or operated by Best Buy, this information may be combined or shared among current or future Best Buy Co., Inc. entities and subsidiaries. The Best Buy Companies operate businesses, retail stores and Web sites under the names Best Buy (BestBuy.com), Best Buy Mobile, (BestBuyMobile.com), Future Shop (FutureShop.ca), Best Buy Canada (BestBuyCanada.ca), Magnolia Audio Video (Magnoliaav.com), Geek Squad (GeekSquad.com), Pacific Sales (PacificSales.com), Speakeasy, (Speakeasy.net), Audio Visions (Avisions.com), Best Buy China (BestBuy.com.cn), Jiangsu Five Star Appliance Co. (Five-Star.cn), among others. 

Each member of the Best Buy Companies, and/or each Web site established by a member of the Best Buy companies, may have its own Privacy Policy which it may modify as needed consistent with these principles. 

**BEST BUY PRIVACY POLICY**

The following Privacy Policy describes the information and privacy practices for Best Buy retail stores, BestBuy.com (the “Best Buy Web site”) and all other locations, occasions or events where your personal information is collected by, or on behalf of, Best Buy. When you provide us your personal information, you consent to the information practices described in this policy.

This Privacy Policy may not apply to Web sites that are accessible through the Best Buy sites. Our Web sites contain links to other sites operated by third parties, including but not limited to third-party sites that display the Best Buy trademarks. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those other sites to learn how they collect, use, share and secure your information.

**Privacy Policy Topics:**Information **COLLECTED** by Best Buy  
**USES** of your personal information  
Personal information **PROVIDED** to Best Buy from third parties  
**SHARING OF** personal information  
**CHOICES** regarding your personal information  
**UPDATING** your personal information  
**SECURITY OF YOUR** personal information  
Cookies, clickstream technology and third party AD providers  
Collection of **CHILDREN's** personal information  
**CONCERNS** about the privacy or security of your personal information  
Privacy policy **CHANGES**

INFORMATION **COLLECTED** BY BEST BUY 

As part of your interaction with Best Buy, we may collect personal information such as: 

  * Contact information, including name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address
  * Purchase information, including credit card number, billing and/pr shipping information 

We may also collect demographic information, including age, personal interests and product preferences. 

While shopping or taking advantage of services available from us, we may ask that you provide personal information. For example, we may request personal information when you: 

  * Purchase products or services
  * Set up an account online
  * Schedule a delivery or an installation
  * Join the RewardZone loyalty program
  * Participate in a sweepstakes, promotion or survey
  * Contact us with a question or concern 
  * Participate in other activities with Best Buy

Back to Top

**USES** OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use the personal information you provide for purposes including, but not limited to: 

  * Fulfilling requests for products, services or information
  * Tracking and confirm online orders
  * Delivering or install products
  * Managing our RewardZone loyalty program
  * Providing customer services 
  * Administering sweepstakes, promotions or surveys
  * Offering new products and services
  * Improving the effectiveness of our Web sites, our marketing endeavors and our services and offers
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Performing other business activities as needed

Back to Top

PERSONAL INFORMATION **PROVIDED** TO BEST BUY FROM THIRD PARTIES

_**Information From/About Friends or Family**_

If you provide us information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason it was provided. Examples include providing a friend's shipping address or using our Send-to-a-Friend option in our marketing e-mails. 

**_Information from Third Parties_**

Best Buy obtains consumer information from third party providers in order to improve the accuracy of our customer database, increase our understanding of our customers, or to identify potential customers. For example, we get updated addresses from the National Change of Address (NCOA) service to ensure we have the correct contact information for our customers. 

Back to Top

**SHARING OF** PERSONAL INFORMATION

Best Buy does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. 

We may need to share your personal information within the Best Buy Companies. These companies may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. 

In addition, Best Buy may share customer information with certain third parties such as our agents, service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as: 

  * Fulfilling customer orders
  * Sending Best Buy marketing communications
  * Delivering packages
  * Scheduling and performing installations
  * Servicing products
  * Maintaining our RewardZone loyalty program
  * Fulfilling subscription services
  * Conducting research, analysis or administering surveys
  * Sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Best Buy
  * Processing credit card payments 

The third parties with whom we conduct business are authorized to use your information only to perform the service for which they are hired. They are required to abide by the terms of our Privacy Policy including taking reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure. 

We may also share aggregated data with third parties for analysis and research purposes. This data does not contain name, address or other personally identifiable information. 

From time to time, we may be required to share personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may share certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of others and ourselves. We may also transfer personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. 

Back to Top

**CHOICES** REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Once you provide your personal information, we may use it to send you offers, promotions and other marketing and customer experience content. 

If you no longer wish to receive these communications, let us know by using whichever of the following methods is appropriate under the circumstances: 

  1. Follow the directions on a marketing e-mail or direct mail marketing communication you receive from us. 
  2. Call 1-888-BEST BUY (1-888-237-8289) with your request and current contact information. 
  3. Send an e-mail with your request and current contact information to: [PrivacyManager@bestbuy.com](mailto:privacymanager@bestbuy.com).
  4. Send a letter with your request and current contact information to:
Best Buy Corporate Campus  
Attn: Customer Care/Privacy  
7601 Penn Avenue South  
Richfield, MN 55423-3645 

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to include your full name, address, phone number and e-mail address, as well as the specific changes you would like to make. This will ensure we correctly identify you in our systems and accurately process your request. 

Best Buy will take the appropriate steps to modify your preferences with respect to our marketing communications. Due to production, mailing and system timelines, it may take some time to process your request. The following guidelines are provided for your convenience: 

  * 10 business days for e-mails
  * 30 business days for phone calls
  * 90 business days for direct mail

Until your requested change takes effect, you may still receive marketing communications from us. If you send us your request by regular mail, please allow extra time for us to receive your notice. 

Although you may have opted not to receive marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order confirmations, product recall notices, RewardZone program membership information or other organization-related communications. 

Back to Top

**UPDATING** YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Best Buy wants your personal information to be accurate and complete. We provide several different methods for you to update your personal information. 

To **update** your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail information: 

  1. If you've created an account on BestBuy.com, you can update your online account information after logging into your account.
  2. Call: 1-888-BEST BUY (1-888-237-8289)
  3. Send a request to: [PrivacyManager@bestbuy.com](mailto:privacymanager@bestbuy.com)
  4. Send a request to:
Best Buy Corporate Campus  
Attn: Customer Care/Privacy  
7601 Penn Avenue South  
Richfield, MN 55423-3645  

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to include your current information and the requested changes. 

Back to Top

**SECURITY OF YOUR** PERSONAL INFORMATION

Whether you are shopping online or in our stores, we use reasonable security measures in place and take reasonable system, process and administrative precautions to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized access of your personal information under our control. Best Buy cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk. 

**_Safe Shopping Policy on BestBuy.com_**

We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. The Best Buy Web site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our Web site such as ordering information including your name, address and credit card number. Information you provide to us via our in-store kiosk does not traverse the public Internet. 

**_Choosing a Personal Password on BestBuy.com_**

When you create an account on BestBuy.com you are required to establish a password. To maximize your level of protection, you should choose at least 6-30 characters, using a combination of both letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information. You have the ability to purchase on our site without creating an account; however, you will need to reenter your personal information each time you use our site in order to make a purchase. 

Back to Top

COOKIES, CLICKSTREAM TECHNOLOGY AND THIRD PARTY AD PROVIDERS

_**Cookies**_

A cookie is a small data file that a Web site or an e-mail may save to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. Our Web sites and e-mails use cookies to create a more personalized shopping experience for visitors to our site. Cookies simulate a continuous connection — they let us "remember" information about your preferences and session, and allow you to move within areas of our Web sites without reintroducing yourself. 

Best Buy uses a third party to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information. Although our cookies may contain a unique user ID, they do not collect or store any personally identifiable information. However, you do have the option of saving your RewardZone membership ID in the cookie so it is easy to remember next time; this option will be found under My Account. 

You may choose to set your Web browser to not accept cookies. However, without enabling your cookies, you will not be able to view, create an account, or make purchases on the Best Buy Web site. 

_**Clickstream Technology**_

Our Web server automatically collects clickstream information such as the address (or URL) of the Web site that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you may have entered on our site, among other things. 

Our Web site may also use other technologies to track which pages our visitors view. This anonymous clickstream data provides our customers with a better shopping experience and helps Best Buy understand how visitors use our Web site. 

_**Third Party Ad Providers**_

The Best Buy Web site uses third party service providers to serve ads across the Internet and to analyze Web site traffic on our behalf. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and your interaction with our ads. These companies may use technologies similar to those outlined above to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails. They may also use information about your visits to our Web site so that we can provide advertisements about goods and services. 

No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. We may share anonymous information with this service provider in an aggregate form, for purposes of analysis and improvement of our site. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by our third-party advertiser, visit <http://www.atlasdmt.com/privacy/>. 

Back to Top

COLLECTION OF **CHILDREN'S** PERSONAL INFORMATION

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. 

Back to Top

**CONCERNS** ABOUT THE PRIVACY OR SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Please contact our Privacy Manager to report a known or suspected privacy or security breach or to submit privacy or security-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days. You may contact us in the following ways: 

  1. Call: 1-888-BEST BUY (1-888-237-8289)
  2. Send a communication to: [PrivacyManager@bestbuy.com](mailto:privacymanager@bestbuy.com)
  3. Send a letter to:  

Best Buy Corporate Campus  
Attn: Customer Care/Privacy  
7601 Penn Avenue South  
Richfield, MN 55423-3645  

Back to Top

PRIVACY POLICY **CHANGES**

As Best Buy continues to improve the services, products and the features we provide, this policy is subject to change. If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here or in other formats for you to review. If we change our information practices or this Privacy Policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a manner not described in the Privacy Policy at the time you provided it, we will give you the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used or shared in that new manner. 

**Changes** : 

  * Addition of brands to list of companies in the Best Buy organization.
  * Revised timeframe to process a direct mail opt-out request from six weeks to 90 business days. 
  * Ability to store RewardZone membership ID in cookies. 
  * Updated mailing address for requests to update your personal information, change your opt-out preferences or contact us with a question or concern.
  * Format, structure and general revisions to improve readability and user-friendliness of content.

Last revision date: November, 20 2007 

Back to Top
